<tips>
	<!-- SHORTCUTS -->
	<tip link="/contents/shortcuts">
		<text>
			You can use the key combination 'CTRL'+'1', 'CTRL'+'2'
			etc. to associate the selection of units or a building
			(not in enemy hands) with a number.
			To reuse the quick selection you just need to
			press '1', '2' etc.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/shortcuts">
		<text>
			To select units of two or more different types when
			stationed inside a building, hold down the 'Shift'
			key and click on their icons.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/shortcuts">
		<text>
			To select a single unit in a group of units inside a
			building, hold down the 'CTRL' key and click on the
			icon of the group you want.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/shortcuts">
		<text>
			To attach units in a structure to a hero hold down the
			'Shift' key while selecting the unit icons and, while
			holding it down, right-click on the hero icon.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/shortcuts">
		<text>
			If you have any doubts during the game or need
			information on some element of the game, you can
			access the help window by pressing the F1 key.
			You can also do this by selecting a unit or building
			and right-clicking on the icon in the top left.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/shortcuts">
		<text>
			To quickly change the selection from one hero to another,
			use the mouse wheel.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/shortcuts">
		<text>
			To send messages to other players during an online game,
			press 'Enter' and write the message in the window that
			will open afterwards (make sure to set the right options
			not to send messages to anyone you do not want).
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/shortcuts">
		<text>
			If you want to review the notes of a mission during
			a battle, press 'F8' or the "Notes" button.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/shortcuts">
		<text>
			If you right-click somewhere on the map while holding
			down the 'CTRL' key, the selected units will head towards
			the chosen point, attacking all enemies they come across.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/shortcuts">
		<text>
			If you want your warriors to attack only units of a certain
			type, hold down the 'CTRL' key and right-click on any unit
			of that type.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/shortcuts">
		<text>
			During a Single player game, you can press the 'F4' key to
			see the game type, the duration and the list of all players
			with their respective scores.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/shortcuts">
		<text>
			You can press the ';' key to toggle the health and stamina
			bars on the screen.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/shortcuts">
		<text>
			By holding down the '\' key, you can make the trees
			transparent so that you can follow the progress of a
			battle in the middle of a dense forest.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<!-- MAP -->
	<tip link="/contents/map">
		<text>
			To open the minimap press the spacebar or the mouse
			wheel.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<!-- LEVEL -->
	<tip link="/contents/stats/level">
		<text>
			The selected unit's level appears at the top of the
			screen, next to the 'L' icon.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/stats/level">
		<text>
			The higher the level of a warrior is, the more damage
			he will deal and the less damage he will suffer.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/stats/level">
		<text>
			Warriors change color depending on the level reached.
			Watch out for golden enemies!
		</text>
	</tip>
	<!-- RUINS (LEVEL-ITEMS) -->
	<tip link="/contents/buildings/Ruins">
		<text>
			Only a hero with a high enough level will be able to
			collect a magic item from the ruins.
			To find out the minimum level required to obtain the
			item from a particular ruin, select it and look at
			the top left of the screen.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<!-- ITEMS -->
	<tip link="/contents/items">
		<text>
			There are many places containing magic objects, where
			new ones appear periodically.
			Go check them every now and then.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/items">
		<text>
			With a single "Finger of death" you can eliminate up to 20
			enemies, and it is not the most powerful item in the game!
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/items">
		<text>
			With the "Battle drums of rage" you can greatly enhance
			the attack power of your army: they are perfect for turning
			the tide of a battle or creating even more synergy with
			specials like "Triple Strike", "Penetration" and "Charge"!
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/items">
		<text>
			Always have a few fast units or units with the "Sneak"
			special ready near the stone piles, so that you can
			secure their control and some "Poison mushrooms" with
			which to easily increase the level of your heroes!
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/items">
		<text>
			You should always equip your heroes with curative items
			such as "Ash of druid heart" or "Healing herbs", this
			way you can greatly reduce the risk of losing them!
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/items">
		<text>
			By depositing 3 of certain objects in the same holder,
			they will fuse into a single, more powerful one.
			This applies to the "Snake skin", the "Eagle feather"
			and the "Boar tooth".
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/items">
		<text>
			If you have heroes that make great use of activable skills,
			equip them with the marvelous "Invigorating dark harp".
		</text>
	</tip>
	<!-- STONEHENGE -->
	<tip link="/contents/buildings/Stonehenge">
		<text>
			The "Divine sacrifice" ritual performed at the stonehenge
			will constantly damage all sages on the map for 1 minute.
			Be careful because even those performing the ritual are
			damaged and you may still need them!
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/buildings/Stonehenge">
		<text>
			The "Starvation" ritual performed at the stonehenge will
			cause a great food reduction for all buildings and
			caravans all over the map.
			It is extremely effective to weaken Germany!
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/buildings/Stonehenge">
		<text>
			The "Earthquake" ritual performed at the stonehenge will
			heavily damage all the strongholds on the map: use it when
			you need to attack one, but be careful not to damage
			yours at the wrong time!
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/buildings/Stonehenge">
		<text>
			The "Teuton horde" ritual performed at the stonehenge
			reduces the population to the minimum and causes a huge
			army of Teutons to appear in every stronghold on the map
			after a delay of 3 minutes. Use this waiting time to
			prepare for the upcoming battle!
		</text>
	</tip>
	<!-- UNITS AND HEROES IN GENERAL -->
	<tip link="/contents/units/Catapult">
		<text>
			Warriors can build catapults, rams and siege towers to
			assault strongholds.
			Select a few of them, then press the "Build siege machine"
			button and find a suitable location for construction.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/feeding">
		<text>
			Warriors need food to regain health and they lose health
			when they do not eat.
			If a unit with food is in a building, it will regain
			much more health.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/stats/stamina">
		<text>
			All units possess 10 stamina with which to use their
			specials.
			When they run out of stamina, they must wait for it to
			regenerate.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/heroes">
		<text>
			Heroes can deploy their warriors in various formations,
			which provide different bonuses.
			It is up to you to choose the most convenient for
			the situation!
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/heroes">
		<text>
			Heroes possess 5 skills that can be improved up to level 10.
			Julius Caesar, as supreme commander, has 6!
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/heroes">
		<text>
			Heroes can use "Divine grace", which helps them instantly
			restore 100 health if they have sufficient stamina.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<!-- HERO SKILLS AND UNIT SPECIALS -->
	<tip link="/contents/heroskills">
		<text>
			With the "Ceasefire" skill you can pass undisturbed among
			enemy armies or flee from a lost battle while minimizing
			casualties.
			You can also use it to capture enemy structures without
			fighting if you have more warriors than the enemy!
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/heroskills">
		<text>
			With the "Defensive cry" skill it is possible to nullify
			the damage of offensive skills such as "Triple strike"
			or "Attack skill", but not that of "Penetration".
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/heroskills">
		<text>
			The "Administration" skill increases the maximum number
			of units that can be attached to the hero, up to 80!
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/heroskills">
		<text>
			The "Battle cry" and "Leadership" skills are perfect to
			make up for a negative level difference as well as
			maximizing the bonus damage and armor provided by
			"Offensive tactics" and "Defensive tactics".
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/heroskills">
		<text>
			The "Quick march" skill is probably the most versatile in
			the game: by moving faster, in fact, you will be able to
			avoid unwanted fights, outflank armies, chase the enemy
			or help allies in trouble.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/specials">
		<text>
			Units with the "Death blow" special, such as Anubis warriors,
			can eliminate an enemy with one strike if that has less than
			50% health after taking damage (it does not affect heroes).
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/specials">
		<text>
			Units with the "Charge" special, such as Gaul horsemen,
			deal 8 times the normal damage if they have not fought
			for at least 10 seconds.
			The damage increase applies after calculation with the
			reduction by armor.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/specials">
		<text>
			Units with the "Cripple" special, such as German axemen,
			can deplete all of an enemy's stamina in one hit (it
			does not affect heroes).
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/specials">
		<text>
			Units with the "Deflection" special, such as hoplites,
			can block enemy attacks, provided that they have
			enough stamina.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/specials">
		<text>
			Units with the "Keen sight" special, such as Tuaregs,
			reveal enemies hiding with "Sneak" and "Invisibility".
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/specials">
		<text>
			Units with the "Toughness" special, such as highlanders,
			increase their maximum health by 5 points per level up,
			thus becoming not only stronger, but also more difficult
			to take down.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/specials">
		<text>
			Units with the "Bleeding attack" special, such as elite
			guards, deal an additional damage equal to 10% of the
			enemy's maximum health with every hit (it does not
			affect heroes).
			As a result, they are lethal against special units or
			when their level is lower than the enemy's.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<!-- SPECIAL UNITS -->
	<tip link="/contents/units/RChariot">
		<text>
			Roman chariots have "Triple strike" and are therefore ideal
			for neutralizing units with low armor.
			Besides, they can become incredibly powerful if they obtain
			the researchable veteran upgrades in the arena.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/units/RLiberatus">
		<text>
			The liberati have the "Bleeding attack" special and are
			therefore perfect for eliminating the special units of
			any enemy.
			With the "Liberati guild" upgrade it is also possible
			to recruit increasingly stronger ones.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/units/GTridentWarrior">
		<text>
			Trident warriors completely restore their health at every
			kill (if they have enough stamina).
			For this reason, sometimes a single one can eliminate
			an entire army.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/units/IMountaineer">
		<text>
			Mountaineers combine "Sneak" and "Offensive tactics" with
			the experience-based upgrades researchable in the arena
			to set up deadly ambushes and dispatch isolated targets
			before these can react.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/units/CWarElephant">
		<text>
			War elephants are slow but have the "Trample" special and
			are therefore capable of wreaking havoc in battles with
			high troop concentrations. Beware of "Spike armor"!
			Furthermore, with the "Mahout school", it is possible
			to train others, without a maximum limit.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/units/BVikingLord">
		<text>
			Viking lords restore their health every time that they
			damage an enemy (if they have enough stamina).
			For this reason, sometimes a single one can eliminate
			an entire army.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/units/EChariot">
		<text>
			Chariots of Osiris are the ultimate weapon to implement
			the "hit and run" tactic as they have the insidious
			"Disease attack" special, with which they can heavily
			weaken the enemy over time.
			The poison is eradicated when health returns to full,
			so make sure the enemy has no way to heal himself!
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/units/TValkyrie">
		<text>
			Valkyries have "Toughness" and "Power strike", a deadly
			combination against low health units like the archers.
			With the "Legendary valkyries" upgrade the new ones
			will be stronger than the previous ones.
			They can also be attached to heroes as they are not limited
			by the "Freedom" special typical of special units.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/units/HMyrmidon">
		<text>
			Myrmidons specialize in killing units with low health, so
			they stand out in ranged fights, but if they reach a good
			number they become almost unbeatable in most situations.
			They can also be attached to heroes as they are not limited
			by the "Freedom" special typical of special units.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<!-- RACES -->
	<tip link="/contents/races/rome">
		<text>
			When you play as Republican Rome, aim to research all the
			upgrades in the arena: by doing so, you will make your
			units better but, above all, you will be able to hire
			Julius Caesar himself after 40 game minutes!
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/races/rome">
		<text>
			When you play as Imperial Rome, your prioritiy has to be
			the unlock of "Military Academy" and of the praetorians.
			Also try to keep plenty of food ready as you will not be
			able to buy it from the tavern.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/races/rome">
		<text>
			When you play as Punic Rome, your units will have the
			"Toughness" special, so make sure to research all the
			training levels in the arena to increase the experience
			and thus the health of your soldiers.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/races/gaul">
		<text>
			When you play as Gaul, aim to fight often as with the
			"Battle tactics" and "Warrior tales" upgrades of the
			arena you will gain huge amounts of experience
			compared to the enemy. Remember that, after 45 game
			minutes, you can also count on the help of the
			legendary Keltill and Larax!
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/races/iberia">
		<text>
			When you play as Iberia, you should keep a defensive
			playstyle, as with the arena upgrades and enchantresses
			you will be able to gain levels without having to fight.
			Meanwhile, exhaust your opponents with mountaineers!
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/races/carthage">
		<text>
			When you play as Carthage, it will be easy for you to obtain
			gold with which to recruit many troops and overwhelm your
			enemies: make sure to research the "Spoils of War" in the
			arena and the "Mercenary pact" in the market as quickly as
			possible and keep your stronghold populated with several
			villages, so that you can sell the inhabitants in exchange
			for more gold.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/races/britain">
		<text>
			When you play as Britain, you'll have various ways to fight
			in unconventional ways, including the ability of your
			druids to hide entire armies with "Invisibility" and
			the chance to trigger various effects like the
			instant elimination of lower-level enemies.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/races/egypt">
		<text>
			When you play as Egypt, try to make the most of the speed
			of your units to grab the resources on the map before the
			enemy: you will secure an advantage that he cannot close.
			Remember that Egyptian units have the most synergistic
			specials in the game, especially "Bleeding attack" and
			"Death blow" of the divine warriors.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/races/germany">
		<text>
			When you play as Germany, research the "Attack focus"
			and "Learning" upgrades as soon as possible, so that you
			can face off against higher-level enemies as equals.
			Your playstyle will have to focus exclusively on
			aggression and attack!
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/races/greece">
		<text>
			When you play as Greece, you will have a huge amount of
			upgrades available not only for your units but also for
			your stronghold. As a result, you will be able to be more
			daring in your attacks while even leaving your stronghold
			unguarded because you can hire sentries, improve the
			gates and even make them indestructible for 2 minutes!
		</text>
	</tip>
	<!-- CAPTURING -->
	<tip link="/contents/capturing">
		<text>
			To capture an ungarrisoned enemy building, you must
			select a group of warriors and right-click on it.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/capturing">
		<text>
			If you find an unprotected enemy caravan, you can capture
			it by selecting some warriors and right-clicking on it.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<!-- BUILDINGS -->
	<tip link="/contents/buildings">
		<text>
			If a building in your stronghold is too damaged, you will
			have to pay to repair it so that it works again.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/buildings/GoldOutpost">
		<text>
			Bring 2000 gold to a gold outpost and watch how the
			amount gradually increases.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/buildings/TradeOutpost">
		<text>
			The trade outpost allows to sell the stored food in
			exchange for gold and vice versa.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/buildings/TrainingOutpost">
		<text>
			A warrior stationed in a training outpost will gain
			experience over time, until reaching level 8.
			Consequently, with the "Nobility" upgrade, it is possible
			to make him reach level 12.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/buildings/RecruitmentOutpost">
		<text>
			Peasants who remain in a recruitment outpost with the
			Carthaginian architecture will be converted to
			Carthaginian macemen.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/buildings/RecruitmentOutpost">
		<text>
			Peasants who remain in a recruitment outpost with the
			Greek architecture will be converted to hoplites.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/buildings/TTent">
		<text>
			You can capture a Teuton tent by eliminating the group
			of riders and archers protecting it.
			When the camp is yours, you will get 10 Teutons.
			Besides, for every 400 food stored in the tent, a new
			Teuton of the type you desire will appear.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/buildings/CTent">
		<text>
			You can capture a Numidian tent by eliminating the group
			of riders and archers protecting it.
			When the camp is yours, you will get 10 Numidians.
			Besides, for every 200 or 400 food stored in the tent,
			a new Numidian of the type you desire will appear.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="/contents/buildings/RTavern">
		<text>
			Once per game, remember to ask for "Tribute": you will
			gain a large amount of gold from all of your outposts.
			This is why it is vital to have control of the map!
		</text>
	</tip>
	<!-- GAME MODES -->
	<tip link="contents/resources">
		<text>
			In a Single player game it is better to keep the stronghold
			population at maximum to gain a higher amount of gold
			(and food, in the case of a German stronghold).
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="contents/fogofwar">
		<text>
			In a Single player game you will have to explore the
			terrain as quickly as you can: you will secure an
			advantage both in resources and logistics.
		</text>
	</tip>
	<tip link="contents/races">
		<text>
			In a Conquest game you will have to think and evaluate in
			which order to subjugate the various territories based on
			the effectiveness of the different bonuses with respect to
			the people you have chosen and the enemy you want to
			conquer.
		</text>
	</tip>
</tips>